<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SZ Planet</title>
    <link>https://szplanet.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SZ Planet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://szplanet.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Non-Passive Reader</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2021/02/09/my-book-tracking-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2021/02/09/my-book-tracking-system/</guid>
      <description>Problem You read a great book, highlighted your favorite quotes, but a few months later, you forgot most of the things in the book and never revisit the notes you took. Does that happen to you? Well, it happens to me all the time. I can vaguely remember the gist and my impressions of the books I&amp;rsquo;ve read, and overtime, I return everything back to my &amp;ldquo;teachers&amp;rdquo;.
I used read a lot of random books, especially detective novels, as a kid until school/textbook reading occupied most of my time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Painting</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2021/01/28/on-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2021/01/28/on-painting/</guid>
      <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s already 2021 and we&amp;rsquo;ve been in pandemic mode for almost a year now. It had been a challenging year for many and a strange year for me as well, with many ups and downs. I had to adjust my life around it for quite a bit, but I&amp;rsquo;m glad to have family around and friends a phone call away (plus the weather in OC is superb).
 &amp;ldquo;My 2020 was an X-Ray that revealed everything that I needed to work on and it showed me everything that was important to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>再观庆余年</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2021/01/13/qingyunian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2021/01/13/qingyunian/</guid>
      <description>“闲”得看剧 去年是出国后十年里第一次有时间回国和家人过年，可是一到就赶上了疫情。虽然哪儿也没去成，但还是在奶奶家开开心心的休息了几天，见到了</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chiffon Cake (戚风蛋糕)</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2020/11/12/chiffon-cake-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2020/11/12/chiffon-cake-recipe/</guid>
      <description>This is a very light and fluffy cake recipe. Preparation time is 15 – 20 minutes and cook time is around 1 hour. The pictured cake was made using a 9” angle food cake pan, but the pan could be of any size and shape. I’m still experimenting and tweaking this recipe to get an optimal cake. Meanwhile, this one is pretty delicious, so enjoy! Ingredients For</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Cross-Stitching</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2020/07/02/cat-cross-stitching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2020/07/02/cat-cross-stitching/</guid>
      <description>I love making things with my hands and cross-stitching has always been something that I wanted to try. During the past couple months, I had time to take a pause in the weekly travels, so I picked up a cross-stitching kit. As a “crazy cat lady”, I decided to go with this cat pattern. At the time of purchase, I thought to myself that I can totally knock this off in a couple days because it looked like a straightforward beginner level kit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexandria, VA</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2019/11/19/alexandria-va-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2019/11/19/alexandria-va-trip/</guid>
      <description>About Alexandria, VA Founded in 1749, Alexandria was a tobacco trading post and because of its unique location along the Potomac river, it was one of the busiest ports in America. Upon arrival at night, I was immediately drawn by the colonial style brick houses, walkable streets, and a variety of boutique shops and restaurants. Quaint is the word I would use – this is exactly what I envisioned a historic New England town would look like!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printed Phone Case with GoPro Mount</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2019/09/22/3d-phone-case-gopro-mount-print/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2019/09/22/3d-phone-case-gopro-mount-print/</guid>
      <description>This print is done on Stratasys Connex 350. Inspiration: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_oog8Lo4rPo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piggy Emoji Mold</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/2019/04/01/3d-piggy-emoji-print/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/2019/04/01/3d-piggy-emoji-print/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Prepare CAD Model I used SOLIDWORKS to create a piggy sketch. Rather than a simple 3D printed part, I added a cylinder shaped pouring cup to make sure that I can pour liquids in the mold later. Additionally, I added a small riser for air to escape after liquids are pour in. To make a clean cast, I introduced some draft to the part as well to reduce sharp edges so that the parts can come off easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read Me</title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/post/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/post/readme/</guid>
      <description>Test test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/top/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Sherry Zhang and I am a Technology Consultant at Accenture. This is a space where I write about things that I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about.
 Projects: Random and fun projects that I enjoy doing in my free time to to be creative and expand my knowledge area.  My Gallery: A Google Photos virtual gallery that I use to keep digital copies of my paintings   Adventures: As a wanderlust, I love going on spontaneous adventures and learning about the world around me, whether it be finding my way in a busy city or camping in the woods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://szplanet.github.io/top/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://szplanet.github.io/top/books/</guid>
      <description>Machine learning学习笔记 Coursera 在线课程 Machine learning 笔记讲师: 吴恩达(Andrew Ng) 课程地址：https://www.coursera.org/lear</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
